

ELHAM DOROODIAN FRONT- END DEVELOPER BUSINESS ANALYST

Date of Birth	\checkmark		♀	0	in	

25 Aug. 1990 e.dorudian@gmail.com +989121774795 Vancouver-B.C. https://github.com/Elhamdorudian https://www.linkedin.com/in/elhamdorudian/

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Highly motivated and dedicated technical business analyst and an enthusiastic front-end developer with an engineering and business background, I have more than six years of professional working experience in IT and ICT sector, and eager to leverage my experience in front-end development.

EDUCATION

- M.Sc. in Business Administration
 Sharif University of Technology Tehran, Iran
- B.Sc. in Mechanical Engineering
 Sep. 2008 May. 2013

 Sharif University of Technology Tehran, Iran

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

Front-End Developer - Technical Business Analyst Mobile Telecommunication Company of Iran (MCI)

Jun. 2019 – Aug. 2022

- Developing web application for the products reference tables to filter and monitor more than 5000 packages (front-end): React.js, CSS, Bootstrap
- Testing web applications including unit, functional and Visual testing: Jest, Testing Library
- Led and supported a 5-member cross-functional team in the "Implementation of a new infrastructure for combo packages" project for 2+ years.
- Assessed technical FRSs¹ of the new "campaign management system".

Business Analyst Jun. 2016 – Feb. 2018 Mobile Telecommunication Company of Iran (MCI)

- Conducted market research and benchmarking to identify 2 underserved customer segments and developed 3 new customized products, increasing the segments' data usage by 25%.
- Monitored recently launched products or campaigns and prepared 10+ reports and dashboards using KPI's such as ARPU, revenue, usage,... for cross and up-sell activities and targeting.
- Presented B2C solutions in products or campaigns, considering promotion opportunities, competitors' behaviors, and existing infrastructure.
- Developed 12+ RFPs of new products resulted in designing 8+ new or updated products.

Business Owner	请 Jul. 2018 − Apr. 2019
FIRUZEH Food Complex	

¹ Functional Requirement Specification

- Developed and implemented sales and marketing plans, promotions and events; created posters, newsletters and assisted with the execution of events which boosted revenue by nearly 25%.
- Established in-person sale meetings and networking that resulted in 3 contracts to supply food to three local businesses.
- Built and increased exposure of the brand through social media platforms like Instagram & Telegram and created a relationship with 8000+ customers.

LICENSEES & CERTIFICATES

- Modern JavaScript, Udemy course Certificates, 2021
- HTML,CSS, and JavaScript for Web Developers, Coursera course, 2020
- 5G, LTE and Intelligent Communications, MCI Workshops, 2020

RELATED COURSES

Business: Microeconomics, Managerial Accounting, Decision Making, Operation Management, Organizational Innovation and Entrepreneurship, Selected Topics in Organizational Development, Organizational Change Management, Agencies Financial Management, Research Methods in Managements,

Engineering: Fundamentals of Programming (C++), Differential Equations, Engineering Mathematics, Numerical Calculations, Robotics and Lab

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

English – Full Professional proficiency
 IELTS: 8 (L=8.5, R=9, W=7.5, S=7.5)

Persian – Native proficiency

SOFTWARE SKILLS

Programming Languages: JavaScript

Web Development: JavaScript, React.js , TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Material UI, Node.js, SASS

Testing: Jest, React Testing Library, Selenium

Administrative: Google Analytics, MS Office, Git, Jira, Visio

REFRENCES

- Mrs. Saeideh Esmaeilifar, Technical Products And Services Manager, Mobile Telecommunication Company of Iran, s.esmaeilifar@mci.ir
- Dr. Sara Banki, Assistant Professor, Graduate School of Management and Economics, Sharif University of Technology, sbanki@sharif.edu
- Dr. Mojtaba Lashkarbolouki, Visiting Lecturer, Graduate School of Management and Economics, Sharif University of Technology, M_Lashkar@sbu.ac.ir